Currently in France

JULIAN Jeanneau

ASPIRING DATA ANALYST

Mobile: +33 (0)6 19 21 63 62 julian.jeanneau@gmail.com

PROFILE

After having worked for over 2 years as a Business Developer at Fuller, I've spent the last few months learning about data analysis (SQL, Python, statistics) aiming for a career change. I also have a strong knowledge of the mobile app industry, with a working experience of more than 5 years in this field.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fuller Inc.

Tokyo, Japan 2018-2020

Société Générale

Prague, Czech Republic 2015-2017

Snapp'

Bordeaux, France 2011-2012

Business Developer

As the Head of Data Acquisition, I took care of the contacts and negotiations with our data providers. I was also in charge of expanding <u>App Ape</u> services abroad, from the strategy to lead generation and customers relations.

Channels Development & Innovation Specialist

Main contact with the Parisian headquarters in the area of innovation. I made market researches, benchmarks and managed projects, including the "Personal Financial Manager" feature for our Czech banking app.

Marketing Assistant

I took care of the communication and marketing plan of <u>FidMe</u> (more than 5 million users). I also was responsible for partnerships, press relations and the customers support.

EDUCATION

IAE de Caen 2012-2014

IUT de Tours 2010-2011

Lycée Brémontier, Bordeaux 2008-2010

Master's Degree in Marketing

Bachelor's Degree in Marketing & IT

Higher Technician Diploma in International Trade

SKILLS